IRINA KUDOSOVA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Full Stack Developer fluent in English, Italian, Russian with international experience in Web Design and Development, currently working toward a certificate in Full Stack Development from the University of Arizona, acquiring skills such as JavaScript, jQuery and ReactJS, excited to join a development team and provide clients, powerful nstruments for their success.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML Bootstrap
CSS MongoDB
JavaScript Express
MySQL ReactJS
NODE.js WordPress

jQuery Adobe Photoshop

LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

English: Fluent (Berlitz CEFR B2)

Russian: Native/Bilingual Italian: Native/Bilingual

EDUCATION

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development University of Arizona | 2019 - 2020

CONTACT

+1 (602) 477-9497

www.irinakudosova.com

irinakudosova@gmail.com

github.com/malinkamell

in linkedin.com/in/irina-kudosova

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

CASINO S.H.I.C.

github | demo

Back-end, Front-end (React), Roulette game (full)

HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | ReactJS| React Bootstrap | Node.js | MongoDB | Express | Socket.io | auth0 | AWS

An online casino platform to play classic casino table games (blackjack, craps, roulette) and slots.

N.E.GYM!

github | demo

Back-end, Front-end

HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | jQuery | Bootstrap | Node.js | MySQL | Express | Sequelize | Handlebars

Content Management System (CMS) that performs CRUD operations with given tools

SPOTLIGHT!

github | demo

Back-end, Front-end (React)

HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | ¡Query | Bootstrap | AJAX | 5 different APIs

A tool to follow your favorite performers' live events

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

CONSULTANT & WEB DESIGNER

Advertising Business Consultants, LLC | Sep 2015 - Aug 2017

Advertising Business Consultant and Digital Marketing Consultant part of Cailean Group.

- Designed 30+ websites for customers using different platforms: Bootstrap, WordPress, Joomla, and Big-Commerce.
- Developed custom e-commerce websites, a custom online training platform, a custom online class booking system, database design, custom administration systems design.

PRODUCT MANAGER

Kalicanthus Entertainment | Milan, Italy | Apr 2007 - May 2011

Started as the Lead Web Designer in the Italian leader gaming company. Italian and then European MMORPG Publisher leader - company acquired by Golden Worlds.

- Developed the first online game portal in Italy with more than 350,000 registered users.
- Built over twenty game websites, including game registration and payment portals, by determining a strategy for completion, designing the template in Adobe Photoshop and creating the site using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and CMSs.
- Strategically determined if team wanted to translate client's existing site or developing a new website, identifying strengths and weaknesses in the original design

Mousee Games, LLC | Unity3D Game Developer | Mar 2012 - Jun 2015

Product Development Specialist | Golden Worlds EMG | Jul 2011-Feb 2012

Product Manager | Intrasoft S.P.A. | Milan, Italy | Jun 2004 - Feb 2006